這渺小的鎮
My little home
我渺小的家
This little town
不缺我一人
They don't need me
這簡單的笑
My simple life
我簡單的命
This simple grin
我已不信任
They betray me
你眼裡的謊
Their lying eyes
虛假的笑容
My cracking shell
心上的刀痕
Their phony smiles
臉上的淚痕
My low morale
感情間的砲火
我抵抗已盡了全力
The emotional warfare
has got the best of me
只要少了我
就不會有糾紛
When you're without me
it'll be easy to share
如果需要我
就假裝我在那兒
And if you need me
you can pretend I'm there
你看不到我
再也不用見到面
You'll never see me
we'll never meet again
就算少了我
你還有其他朋友
'Cause even without me,
you have your other friends
我總好奇
I wonder how
他們會怎麼想
they'd think of me
如果我就此離去
if I left them
他們哪會在乎
They wouldn't mind
他們哪會介意
they wouldn't care
我也沒給他們機會
I wouldn't let them
沒有歌謠
No serenade
沒有音樂
no lullaby
沒有故事
no metaphor
能讓我回頭
can change my mind
畢竟遙遠的那端
不過是我的「很久很久以前」
'Cause somewhere out there
is my "Once upon a time"
只要少了我
就不會有糾紛
When you're without me
it'll be easy to share
如果需要我
就假裝我在那兒
And if you need me
you can pretend I'm there
你看不到我
再也不用見到面
You'll never see me
we'll never meet again
就算少了我
你還有其他朋友
'Cause even without me,
you have your other friends
只要少了我...
When you're without me...
如果需要我...
And if you need me...
你看不到我...
You'll never see me...
就算少了我...
'Cause even without me...